# SELIN CETINKAYA SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# CONTACT

AUSTIN, TX

SELIN.S.CETINKAYA@GMAIL.COM

646-912-3150

**SELINSCETINKAYA.COM** 

LINKEDIN

**GITHUB** 

## **PROJECTS**

- o Project 1: Stock Up is a web app that allows users to categorize their shopping lists in a convenient display. I used Airtable to create an API used for creating, editing, and deleting list items dynamically, making running errands just a little bit more pleasant.
- Project 2: Collaboreatery is a full-stack web-app for users to search, add, and "favorite" restaurants based on location and cuisine. The purpose of this project was to learn about building databases using Mongo as well as working in a group setting.
- Project 3: Impression is a full-stack photo-sharing web-app where users can upload, "like", and comment on photos. I used a React front-end and a Ruby on Rails backend to build this app

## SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML
- React
- CSS

## SUMMARY

I am a quick-thinking software engineer with a background in real estate and a passion for learning. Consistent, communicative, and thorough, I enjoy customizing solutions for a specific client or situation. With years of experience as a realtor in Austin, TX, I am skilled at quickly coming up with unique solutions to problems and look forward to future opportunities to grow as a software engineer.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **AUDIOEYE**

IMPLEMENTATION DEVELOPER | NOV 2021 - PRESENT

- Use internal tools to test website accessibility and write Javascript functionality to improve that accessibility abiding by Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) principles.
- Work closely with Quality Assurance testers to ensure that websites can both pass internal tool tests as well as perform accurately in a real-world setting.

#### **GENERAL ASSEMBLY**

FELLOW | FEB 20121 - MAY 2021

- Worked both collaboratively and independently to build functional applications, getting hands on experience with every step of the development process
- Planned, designed, built, and deployed full-stack web applications

#### HONEYCO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN | APRIL 2016 - JULY 2017

- Provided daily support for two websites assisting the CTO with migrating on from Rails to React, while addressing bug fixes and general maintenance for another Rails site.
- Worked closely with the CEO and CTO to create timelines and planning strategies for general company growth.

# **EDUCATION**

**BACHELOR OF ARTS, MAJOR IN SOCIOLOGY** 

HUNTER COLLEGE | 2015 - 2017

GPA: 3.94

WESLEYAN UNIVERSITY UNDERGRAD | 2013 - 2015

GENERAL ASSEMBLY SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE PROGRAM | FEB-MAY 2021

#### **DESIGN 101 COURSE**

DESIGN LAB | SEPT 2020

- React
- Rails
- SQL

- Python
- Ruby